<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on JVL Codex</title>
    <link>https://mynewhugosite.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on JVL Codex</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mynewhugosite.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Concepts to Understand Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://mynewhugosite.com/posts/reinforcement_learning_basic_concepts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mynewhugosite.com/posts/reinforcement_learning_basic_concepts/</guid>
      <description>In which I explain what is reinforcement learning, where it fits in the whole as a machine learning paradigm. Some of the basic concepts of reinforcement how they interact with each other and some possible directions.
 Introduction Reinforcement learining — RL — seems to be the hot topic in machine learning nowadays, it&amp;rsquo;s the basis for the algorithm that beat the Go champion, a game in which, pundits claim, a computer would not be able to beat a human within this century and also it is what makes you spend more when shopping online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning How to Make a Blog</title>
      <link>https://mynewhugosite.com/posts/learning_how_to_make_a_blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mynewhugosite.com/posts/learning_how_to_make_a_blog/</guid>
      <description>In which I explain how I made this website and everything I&amp;rsquo;ve learned in the process including html, css, design, webdesign, hugo, go and Javascript. If you are like me learning how to create a blog post please have a seat a join in this incredible storytell.
 Here&amp;rsquo;s an example blog post.
 Este é um blockquote este não sei será uma continuação
 Essa é uma Rubrica   em html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://mynewhugosite.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mynewhugosite.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About me Hi there, my name is João Victor Laitano Coelho. I was raised and I&amp;rsquo;m currently living in SC-Florianópolis, south of Brazil. Graduated at UFSC in Electrical Engineering, and now I&amp;rsquo;m doing a masters degree. I&amp;rsquo;ve been working as a data scientist at an up and coming startup for the last two years.
Now  Currently my studies in machine learning have been about Reinforcement Learning. I&amp;rsquo;m learning a little about web development so I can start this blog up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
